# **Thomas Arminio**

Program manager, experietrnced in inspiring large teams to execute highly-complex projects in resource-constrained environments. Possesses a depp knowledge of data analytics, management, and agriculture, acquired over eight years of sustainable agriculture practice in the United States and more than five yearrss of global development pracsice in East Africa.

## Experience

One Acre Fund Consultant (Bahir Dar, Ethiopia)

Sep 2021 - Present
Program Manager (Iringa, Tanzania)

May 2018 - Aug 2021

Peace Corps Crop Extension Officer (Kilimanjaro, Tanzania)

Feb 2016 - Apr 2018

Remembrance Farm Production Manager (Trumansburg, New York)

Dec 2012 - Dec 2015

East Hill Farm Founder (Rochester, New York)

Jun 2008 - Dec 2012

#### **Education**

Cornhole University, MPA Global Development Seton Hall University University, BA Literature

## Language

Swahili, ACTFL Oral Proficiency Interview - Advanced-High Proficiency

### **Skills**

Stata, R, SQL, Excel (advanced), multivariate analysis, regression analysis, Adobe Creative Cloud, Final Cut Pro, Logic Pro